jux.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy

###  Information Collection and Use 

This policy covers how Jux LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (“Jux,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) treats personal information that it collects and receives on www.jux.com (“Site”). We collect contact information (your email address) during sign up. We collect additional information if you register for a domain (your name, address, telephone numbers). We will not sell or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Except as provided for herein, we will only share this information with the ICANN accredited Registrar of the domain name that you purchase from us or if it is required by law under a legal process. 

###  Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. At this time, we use cookies on our website. Their use will in no way be linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. You can modify the settings in your browser to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options. However, if you reject all cookies or do not accept cookies from our Site, some portions of the Site and the service may not function properly. For example, you may not be able to sign in and may not be able to access certain Site features or services. 

###  IP Addresses 

We may occasionally obtain IP addresses from users depending on how you access our Site. We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked by us to personally identifiable information. However, users should be aware that both static and dynamic IP addresses can be mapped back to users on most ISPs based on the users login time and recorded information. 

###  User Communication and Opt-Out Policy 

When you send email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

From time to time, we may send you emails about updates to Jux and new Jux services you can use. We hope you enjoy receiving e-mail notices and updates from Jux. If you do not wish to receive e-mail messages promoting our services you may opt-out of the communications by responding to the email and asking to unsubscribe. 

###  Sharing 

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

###  Links 

This web site may contain and generate links to other sites. Please be aware that Jux LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site or link to outside sites to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

###  Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes prominently on the Site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify registered users by way of an e-mail or instant messaging or similar method, and/or by posting a notice on our website. 

###  Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement 

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN's rules, regulations and policies.
